https://strathpeffergolf.com/privacy-cookies/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
'Privacy Matters'Privacy Policy Strathpeffer Spa Golf Club is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Contact us at admin@strathpeffergolf.com if you have any questions or problems regarding the use of your Personal Data and we will gladly assist you.By using this site or/and our services, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.Table of ContentsDefinitions used in this PolicyData protection principles we followWhat rights do you have regarding your Personal DataWhat Personal Data we gather about youHow we use your Personal DataWho else has access to your Personal DataHow we secure your dataInformation about cookiesContact informationDefinitionsPersonal Data – any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.Processing – any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data.Data subject – a natural person whose Personal Data is being Processed.Child – a natural person under 16 years of age.We/us (either capitalised or not) – Strathpeffer Spa Golf ClubData Protection PrinciplesWe promise to follow the following data protection principles:Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.Data Subject’s rightsThe Data Subject has the following rights:Right to information – meaning you have to right to know whether your Personal Data is being processed; what data is gathered, from where it is obtained and why and by whom it is processed.Right to access – meaning you have the right to access the data collected from/about you. This includes your right to request and obtain a copy of your Personal Data gathered.Right to rectification – meaning you have the right to request rectification or erasure of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete.Right to erasure – meaning in certain circumstances you can request for your Personal Data to be erased from our records.Right to restrict processing – meaning where certain conditions apply, you have the right to restrict the Processing of your Personal Data.Right to object to processing – meaning in certain cases you have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data, for example in the case of direct marketing.Right to object to automated Processing – meaning you have the right to object to automated Processing, including profiling; and not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated Processing. This right you can exercise whenever there is an outcome of the profiling that produces legal effects concerning or significantly affecting you.Right to data portability – you have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a machine-readable format or if it is feasible, as a direct transfer from one Processor to another.Right to lodge a complaint – in the event that we refuse your request under the Rights of Access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. If you are not satisfied with the way your request has been handled please contact us.Right to withdraw consent – you have the right withdraw any given consent for Processing of your Personal Data.Data we gatherInformation you have provided us withThis might be your e-mail address, name, billing address, home address etc – mainly information that is necessary for delivering you a product/service or to enhance your customer experience with us. We save the information you provide us with in order for you to comment or perform other activities on the website. This information includes, for example, your name and e-mail address.Information automatically collected about youThis includes information that is automatically stored by cookies and other session tools. For example, your IP address, your Email address (if any is given) etc. This information is used to improve your customer experience. When you use our services or look at the contents of our website, your activities may be logged.Information from our partnersWe gather information from our trusted partners with confirmation that they have legal grounds to share that information with us. This is either information you have provided them directly with or that they have gathered about you on other legal grounds.Publicly available informationWe might gather information about you that is publicly available.How we use your Personal DataWe use your Personal Data in order to:provide our service to you. This includes for example providing you with products and services that you have requested; providing you with promotional items at your request and communicating with you in relation to those products and services; communicating and interacting with you; and notifying you of changes to any services.enhance your customer experience;fulfil an obligation under law or contract.We use your Personal Data on legitimate grounds and/or with your Consent.On the grounds of entering into a contract or fulfilling contractual obligations, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:to identify you;to provide you a service or to send/offer you a product;to communicate either for sales or invoicing.On the ground of legitimate interest, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:to send you personalised offers* (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);to administer and analyse our client base in order to improve the quality, variety, and availability of products/ services offered/provided;to conduct questionnaires concerning client satisfaction.As long as you have not informed us otherwise, we consider offering you products/services that are similar or same to your browsing behaviour to be our legitimate interest.With your consent we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:to send you newsletters and campaign offers (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);for other purposes we have asked your consent for;We Process your Personal Data in order to fulfil obligation rising from law and/or use your Personal Data for options provided by law. We reserve the right to anonymise Personal Data gathered and to use any such data. We will use data outside the scope of this Policy only when it is anonymised. We save the information gathered about you for as long as needed for accounting purposes or other obligations deriving from law only for as long as is in accordance with approved practices.We might process your Personal Data for additional purposes that are not mentioned here, but are compatible with the original purpose for which the data was gathered. To do this, we will ensure that:the link between purposes, context and nature of Personal Data is suitable for further Processing;the further Processing would not harm your interests andthere would be appropriate safeguard for Processing.Who else can access your Personal DataWe do not share your Personal Data with strangers. Personal Data about you is in some cases provided to our trusted partners in order to either make providing the service to you possible or to enhance your customer experience.We only work with Processing partners who are able to ensure adequate level of protection to your Personal Data. We will only disclose your Personal Data to third parties or public officials when we are legally obliged to do so. We might disclose your Personal Data to third parties if you have consented to it or if there are other legal grounds for it.How we secure your dataWe do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymising and encyrption technologies when dealing with your data.Even though we try our best we can not guarantee the security of information. However, we promise to notify suitable authorities of data breaches. We will also notify you if there is a threat to your rights or interests. We will do everything we reasonably can to prevent security breaches and to assist authorities should any breaches occur.Cookies and other technologies we useWe use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyse customer behaviour, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalise and enhance your experience with us.A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.Your can find out more information about our cookie policy here.Contact InformationPlease visit our Contact Us page for detailsChanges to this Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy.Last modification was made 24/05/2020. This website uses cookies to improve your experience. Continue browsing or choose accept if you agreed to the use of cookies. Read MoreCookie SettingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website. Scroll to top
HomeThe ClubExpand child menuExpand ClubhouseEvents CalendarClubhouse GalleryClub ShopCoffee MorningsFunction Room HireWedding EventsThe CourseExpand child menuExpand Course GuideCourse GalleryVirtual TourScorecard & MapMembershipsExpand child menuExpand Rates & JoiningReciprocal CoursesVisitorsExpand child menuExpand Open CompetitionsGreen Fees & HiresTee-Time ReservationTestimonialsGroups & SocietiesBusiness & CorporatesAccommodationNewsContact UsExpand child menuExpand Contact FormsMembers Area
